When you've got to go, you've got to go.
人有三急，不得不急。
At least that's the old saying!
至少老话说得好！
It refers to the often inconvenient need for a person to visit the toilet. It can happen to us all.
这句话指的是人们常常有需要上厕所的不便需求，我们每个人都可能遇到。
There you are, out and about - when suddenly your bladder informs you that you need to spend a penny.
比如你在外面四处走动时，突然膀胱提醒你需要“花一便士”（上厕所）。
The logical thing to do is tie a knot in it until you get to your destination, but what if you're busting?
合理的做法是先憋着到目的地，但要是你憋不住了呢？
That's when you head straight to the nearest public lavatory. But in the UK, that might prove tough.
这时你会直接奔向最近的公共厕所，但在英国，这可能很难。
Public loos in the UK appear to be going down the toilet.
英国的公共厕所似乎正在“掉进马桶里”（逐渐消失）。
At least 673 public restrooms across the UK have not been maintained by their councils since 2010, according to figures obtained by the BBC under the Freedom of Information Act.
根据BBC依据《信息自由法》获取的数据，自2010年以来，英国至少有673间公共厕所未得到地方议会的维护。
That means there are 13% fewer places where a person can have a tinkle.
这意味着人们能“小解”的地方减少了13%。
Why is this?
为什么会这样？
It's a combination of two factors.
两个原因导致了这一情况。
Councils in the UK are facing enormous pressure to reduce spending.
英国地方议会面临巨大的削减开支压力。
By 2020, they will have experienced a 54% reduction in funding from central government, according to the UK's Local Government Association.
据英国地方政府协会称，到2020年，它们从中央政府获得的资金将减少54%。
Secondly, there is no legal requirement for a local authority to provide a location to relieve yourself.
其次，法律并未要求地方当局提供如厕场所。
As a result, toilet upkeep often gets 'flushed' to save money.
因此，为了省钱，厕所维护常常被“冲掉”（忽略）。
Many councils have handed over the running of some toilets to parish councils, private companies or community groups.
许多议会已将部分厕所的运营移交给教区议会、私营企业或社区团体。
Councils have a 'moral responsibility' to provide access to public toilets, Raymond Martin of the British Toilet Association told the BBC.
英国厕所协会的雷蒙德・马丁告诉BBC，议会有提供公共厕所的“道德责任”。
And it would seem that they know it, too.
似乎议会也意识到了这一点。
Despite closures, many councils have backed schemes to allow the public to use private business facilities to do their business.
尽管有关闭现象，许多议会仍支持允许公众使用私营企业设施如厕的计划。
The City of London has run a community toilet scheme since 2012, giving the public free access to their toilets during trading hours, and Derry City and Strabane District Council's Community Toilet Scheme offers businesses in their remit a financial incentive to allow the public to powder their noses.
伦敦金融城自2012年起实施“社区厕所计划”，在营业时间内公众可免费使用其厕所；德里市和斯特拉班区议会的“社区厕所计划”则向辖区内企业提供经济激励，鼓励它们允许公众“补妆”（如厕）。
In addition, Network Rail, owner and operator of the railway infrastructure in Britain, has plans in the pipeline to scrap entry fees at all of its station toilets from 2019.
此外，英国铁路基础设施的所有者和运营商“铁路网公司”已计划从2019年起取消所有车站厕所的入场费。
So it seems all hope is not lost.
所以，希望并未完全破灭。
Despite the fact that council-run public toilet numbers are down, there are alternatives available.
尽管议会管理的公共厕所数量减少，但仍有其他选择。
Rather than having to cross your legs, look around. You can always find somewhere that will let you polish the porcelain.
与其憋着，不如环顾四周——你总能找到某个地方让你“擦拭瓷器”（上厕所）。